Date Ordered: 2017/03/22 08:40:34 +0000
Job: j230828
Name: OpenStreetMap: Lille, France Metro Region
Data Listing Token: 4f7dacf9-7c32-4cb6-80c8-5f3232a93da6
Job Token: 13c2f64a-3f25-453c-8698-f41d2393f5d6


### Contents of Data Order ###

# Data #
The Data folder contains the data that was ordered. The file extension depends on the type of data requested.

# Misc #
The Misc folder contains any additional information the provider included with the dataset. If the provider did not include any additional information, this folder will be empty.

# Description #
The Description File is a copy of the dataset's description as seen on the data listing when the data was ordered.

# Read Me #
The file you are currently reading.

# License #
The License agreement associated with the downloaded data. The license agreement contains information on use restrictions, liability, and disclaimers.