Date Ordered: 2017/03/23 08:58:39 +0000
Job: j231008
Name: OpenStreetMap: New York, NY Metro Region
Data Listing Token: dc675faa-3535-4083-a395-7448188b763c
Job Token: ed8ab0c7-b90d-48d8-ab80-cc21ec5eddc3


### Contents of Data Order ###

# Data #
The Data folder contains the data that was ordered. The file extension depends on the type of data requested.

# Misc #
The Misc folder contains any additional information the provider included with the dataset. If the provider did not include any additional information, this folder will be empty.

# Description #
The Description File is a copy of the dataset's description as seen on the data listing when the data was ordered.

# Read Me #
The file you are currently reading.

# License #
The License agreement associated with the downloaded data. The license agreement contains information on use restrictions, liability, and disclaimers.